[{"answer": "Hi, Mia.  Hows it going", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Im OK thanks.  How about you", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Hi, Mia.  Hows it going", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Im doing good.  You dont seem yourself.  Whats the matter", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Im OK thanks.  How about you", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Well, honestly, Im having some problems at work", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Im doing good.  You dont seem yourself.  Whats the matter", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Oh, really?  What kind of problems?  Is it a co-worker", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Well, honestly, Im having some problems at work", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " No, its nothing like that.  Im just feeling really stressed out.  Work i", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Oh, really?  What kind of problems?  Is it a co-worker", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Why are you feeling so stressed out at work", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 22, "question": " No, its nothing like that.  Im just feeling really stressed out.  Work i", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " I just feel in the last few months that Ive had more and more projects an", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Why are you feeling so stressed out at work", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " I knew youd been busy, but I didnt realize it was that bad", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 27, "question": " I just feel in the last few months that Ive had more and more projects an", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Ive been working so much overtime.  I usually come in around 7:30 and stay til", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 31, "question": " I knew youd been busy, but I didnt realize it was that bad", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": "0 or 8:00 in the evening", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Ive been working so much overtime.  I usually come in around 7:30 and stay til", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Are you serious?  Its not healthy to be working such long hours", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": "0 or 8:00 in the evening", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I know.  By the time I get home, I have no time to cook dinner, do any chores, o", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Are you serious?  Its not healthy to be working such long hours", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Oh, no", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 39, "question": " I know.  By the time I get home, I have no time to cook dinner, do any chores, o", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Im coming in on the weekends too, so I feel like I practically live in the office", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Oh, no", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Cant you just delegate some of the tasks or put them off until later", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Im coming in on the weekends too, so I feel like I practically live in the office", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No, I feel like theres so much pressure on me to get it all done now and by myself", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Cant you just delegate some of the tasks or put them off until later", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Pressure from where", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No, I feel like theres so much pressure on me to get it all done now and by myself", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Upper management.  They want everything done immediately", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Pressure from where", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": "Im sorry to hear that things are so stressful for you", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Upper management.  They want everything done immediately", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Thanks.  I just feel so burned out right now.  I dont know how much more I ca", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Im sorry to hear that things are so stressful for you", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": "Yeah, the rat race can do that to you.  Have you thought about doing anythin", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Thanks.  I just feel so burned out right now.  I dont know how much more I ca", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Like what", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Yeah, the rat race can do that to you.  Have you thought about doing anythin", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Maybe talking to your bosses and explaining that things are too stressful, o", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Like what", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " I dont think they would listen.  I could try yoga, but I dont really have time", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Maybe talking to your bosses and explaining that things are too stressful, o", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " You really should try to make some time.  It might help", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 60, "question": " I dont think they would listen.  I could try yoga, but I dont really have time", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Maybe.  Im considering even changing jobs and moving so that I can have ", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 61, "question": " You really should try to make some time.  It might help", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Really?  Where", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Maybe.  Im considering even changing jobs and moving so that I can have ", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I dont know.  Somewhere quieter  the country maybe.  Maybe I could find a les", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Really?  Where", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Thats not a bad idea.  All this stress will make you sick", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 70, "question": " I dont know.  Somewhere quieter  the country maybe.  Maybe I could find a les", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " I know.  I need to relax more and have more me time", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Thats not a bad idea.  All this stress will make you sick", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Well, if theres anything I can do to help, let me know", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 75, "question": " I know.  I need to relax more and have more me time", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thanks, Susan.  Just listening helps", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Well, if theres anything I can do to help, let me know", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I hope things around here become less stressful or that you can find a way out", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Thanks, Susan.  Just listening helps", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Thanks.  I appreciate it", "docId": "03-09", "aSentId": 78, "question": " I hope things around here become less stressful or that you can find a way out", "qSentId": 77}]
